Phong Yang

Clinical Systems Consultant



(561) 7*****4



tubphooj@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/phong-yang

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Microsoft Active Directory Security

Content Administrator for Sharepoint,
Confluence

Data Analytics – PowerBI Builder, Microsoft SSRS, Crystal Reports

Microsoft SQL Database Management

VM Tools - ESXI

Citrix XenApp/XenDesktop

Infor Cloverleaf

DICOM and HL7 integrations, validation, testing, activation, monitoring

EMR Experience: Cerner, Meditech, eCW, PatientKeeper

Lumedx Applications Suite (Apollo, Analytics Manager, HealthView Analytics)

Cloud PACS Experience: Nuance Powershare, Viztek Opal, Medidata, Scimage

Voice Recognition: Dolbey Fusion, Nuance PowerScribe

GE Centricity Applications - PACS, DMS, CA1000, RA1000, Universal Viewer, ZFP, Cardio Workflow (CCW)

GE Enterprise Archive

GE Muse EKG, CardioDay, CareScape

GE MacLab & CardioLab

Agfa Impax PACS

Phillips Xcelera PACS

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A highly motivated, goal-oriented IT professional with 17 years of experience in clinical imaging systems management, implementations, and support. Subject Matter Expert on all clinical systems and integrations. Led efforts on strategic planning, integration development, documentation, workflow optimization, and training. Ability to effectively communicate and partner with key stakeholders, vendors, and customers to establish successful solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Enterprise Consulting Imaging Systems Administrator

HCA Healthcare – East FL Div. | Miami-ft Lauderdale Area, FL | July 2010 – Present

- Division leader for Cardiovascular Imaging solutions, serving 14 hospitals in HCA East
 Florida
- Provide consultation and guidance for imaging equipment purchases and integration capabilities, with focus on standardization.
- Review and approve Capital Expense Requests to ensure equipment meets information protection standards, integrations, and software options to meet clinical and IT needs.
- Manage a rolling 5-Year budget plan for end-of-life equipment refresh, includes servers, workstations, and clinical imaging equipment.
- Designated Project Lead for small and large projects throughout the division. Managed all project stages, from initiation, establishing scope, identifying teams and stakeholders, development, implementation, to product activation; including documentation, identifying success metrics, and end user/customer follow-up and ongoing review for improvement opportunities.
- Earned Subject Matter Expert (SME) on products we support and integrations.
- Self-taught Data Analytic tools, PowerBI, SSRS, and SAP Crystal Reports. Built data models to produce meaningful content for leadership to make impactful decisions. Developed Success Metrics, KPIs and Paginated Reports.
- Led division to become the first to successfully implement a cardiovascular physician reporting application, resulting in accurate procedure and supplies documentation for coding and billing; leading to increased reimbursement.
- Saved the organization over \$300,000 in equipment refresh and service maintenance
 costs by eliminating antiquated technology and implementing a consolidated solution
 that efficiently handles volume with less overhead, improving efficiency with custom
 routing scripts.
- Key imaging resource during development of HCA's CareAssure Program, an outcomes
 base nurse navigation application that triggers potential patients with specific heart
 conditions.
- Led efforts to standardize Echocardiology physician reporting to reach IAC (Intersocietal Accreditation Commission) Accreditation, as a result, increasing patient referral opportunities and reimbursements per exam.
- Developed a work stream for free-standing ambulatory imaging services to integrate with the enterprise imaging systems, from patient registration in EMR, patient worklists, workflow consultation, and results integration.
- Led HL7 and API integration efforts with vendors and EMR teams.
- Compose and updated clinical and technical documentations: Workflow diagrams,
 Work aids, IT systems (application and network) diagrams, implementation toolkits,
 iSAM (Information System Access Management), and end user competencies.

Phong Yang

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Leadership, Responsibility, Commitment to customers and colleagues

Project Management

Creative solutions for complex issues

Dynamic, team-oriented approach

Developing workflow optimization & process improvement

Clinical and Technical Documentation
Writing

Ability to communicate, educate, motivate and delegate to reach goals and objectives

Experienced trainer for all end users

Excellent opportunity identification and proactive problem-solving abilities

Focus on quality assurance and ongoing review

Strong work ethics, dedicated and committed

AWARDS AND ACHEIVEMENTS

HCA Aspiring Manager - 2013

Employee of the Month - May 2011

Exemplary Employee - 2010 and 2011

Hero 365 (Employee of the Year) – 2018

Frequent Peer-to-Peer Recognitions for "Raising the Bar" and "Unlock Possibilities"

Consistently receives highest mark "Exceptional" on Annual Employee Performance Reviews

REFERENCES

Available upon request

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

Imaging Systems Administrator

HCA FL JFK Medical Center | Atlantis, FL | June 2006 - July 2010

- Led the initial implementation of PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) in this 435-bed hospital, transitioning analog film to digital diagnostic imaging.
- Was the single IT point of support and training for hardware and applications for 22 radiologists over 200 Radiology department system users.
- Liaison between IT, Radiology, physicians, clinical departments, vendors and HCA Division and Corporate.
- Developed and implemented new competencies, policies and procedures for PACS.
- Implemented the first successful Dolbey Radiology Voice Recognition dictation system in East Florida Division. Transitioned Radiologists from recorded dictations to voice recognition. Achieved 100% compliance. A major improvement for patient care, reducing turnaround time and improving physician efficiency.
- Appointed project lead for several Division wide projects which lead to a promotion to a consultant role, focus on systems and workflow standardization: Muse (Digital EKG system), DMS (Cardiovascular Information System), MRS (Mammography Reporting System), PowerShare (teleradiology), Dolbey (Voice Recognition), and many others...
- Managed monthly security patching on imaging systems and modalities

PACS Assistant Administrator

Florida Hospital - Heartland Division | Sebring, FL | May 2005 - June 2006

- Responsible for day-to-day operation of PACS equipment including radiology workflow, routing, fetching, archiving, and integration with the Radiology Information System.
- Developed a strong understanding of PACS Imaging Systems and integrations, AGFA Impax
- Administered PowerScribe Voice Recognition System
- Enhanced knowledge of Databases, Servers, Operating Systems, and Networking.
- Restructured and applied strict user management policies
- Oversaw and coordinated PACS training of radiology staff, created education and competency tools.

EDUCATION

University of Phoenix | 2010 - 2012

Master in Business Administration - Technology Management

Appalachian State University | 2001 - 2005

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science